Guide to the Gödel Editorial Project Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, Accession ARCH-2005-262
  - Final corrections to IN 49a (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Final corrections to 1952 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Final corrections to IN 58, 72 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Final corrections to 1962 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Final corrections to 1964 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Final corrections to 1972 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Final corrections to IN 72a (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Introductory notes to 1972a.1,2 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Introductory note 1972a.2 (Feferman and Solovay) (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - 1972a Notes 1, 2 (Kreisel's version) (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Webb – introductory note to Gödel 1972a #3 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Webb – note on 1972a (3) (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Final corrections to 1972a (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Fenstad – notes on Gödel 1974 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Final corrections to IN 74 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Final corrections to 1974 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - New References, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Corrections to the references Vol. II, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Herbrand – Chevalley [photocopies of original documents] (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Herbrand – Chevalley 3 Dec. 1930 [photocopies of original documents] (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Herbrand, Noether – Chevalley 12 Dec. 1931 [photocopy of original document] (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Herbrand correspondence [photocopies of original documents] (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Herbrand general [photocopies of original documents] (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Herbrand – Groupe Herbrand [photocopies of original documents] (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Herbrand references (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Notes accompanying "L'oeuvre logique de Jacques Herbrand…" 1981 (JvH) (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Kreisel – JvH correspondence 1986 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Gödel Works Vol. III Planning meeting, Phila. March 1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Oxford Press projects (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Gödel Nachlass Inventory – TEX, vol. III (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - TEX samples – shorthand/longhand (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - [To file: photocopy of Gödel item (04038) and correspondence of S. Kleene 1988] (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Gödel project – current (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Gödel Project editorial meeting, March 1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Items from Gödel Nachlass (copies) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Gödel Project material from Zurich, Winter 1987 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - [To file: copy of Gödel 1958 and correspondence of Dirk Siefkes (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Gödel refile (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Solomon Feferman – Gödel Project – Things to do (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Gödel Project – editorial correspondence, work, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Finalizing Vol. II – memo to eds, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Gödel Works Vol. II – finalizing material from JD (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Proposed translation of the Gödel Volume [to Italian], 1986 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Gödel group meeting, Jan. 1985 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Working agenda July 1986 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - [Review of Volume I, 1987] (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Assorted printouts and copies of final text and/or material for volumes (Box 6)
  - List of appendices, cover sheet for Appendix A, Contents V. II (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Appendix B: Reviews (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Appendix C: CV's (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Appendix D1 and D2 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Appendices E, F, and G (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - *1946/9 Kant/Relativity Man. A (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - *1946/9 Kant/Relativity Man. B (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - *1946/9 Kant/Relativity Man. C (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Appendix H and cover sheets for I (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Appendix J, K and L (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Printouts of text (Box 6)
  - ASL/NSF Audit Response Gödel Project May 27, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - ASL/NSF Audit Materials May 13, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Gödel Project Budgets 1984- (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Materials from Henson (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - NSF – Gödel Project audit (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Materials from CD [assorted reports, minutes, assignments, etc.] (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Gödel – Tarski correspondence(photocopies and typescript copies) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - G. Kreisel [published versions of Gödel's letters to] (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Dawson "A meeting of minds: the Gödel editorial project" (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - G. K. reviews of K. G. Works II (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Heading lists [of Gödel's notebooks] (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Gödel Works, contract for Volume III and IV (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Memo re TEX fonts (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Files of van Heijenoort:
    - Notebook "Gödel" [very few entries] (Box 7)
    - Gödel: photocopies of original papers (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Partial folder list (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Originals [actually contains photocopies of articles] (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Textual notes (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Reviews, computer text July 8, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Bauer-Mengelberg corrections to JWD translations (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Proofreading corrections by JvH of Dawson translations (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Nevarietur (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - IN 1929 and 1930 – correspondence, 1983-85 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - IN 1929 and 1930 – final draft (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - IN 1929 and 1930 – general (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - IN 1929 and 1930 – materials (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - IN 1929 and 1930 – material (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - IN 1929 and 1930 – remarks by Dawson (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - IN 1929 and 1930 – Dreben's notes of October 15, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - IN 1929 and 1930 – SF's remark on draft of May 25, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - IN 1929 and 1930 – remarks by Feferman (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - IN 1929 and 1930 – July 10, 1984 draft, SF's remarks (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - IN 1929 and 1930 – remarks by Kleene and Moore (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - 1929 Vienna University text (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - 1929 Princeton text (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - van Heijenoort, Differences between the Vienna and Princeton texts, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - van Heijenoort, Remarks on the variora…, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Gödel dissertation, computer text May 1982 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Gödel dissertation, corrections by JvH to computer text of May 1982 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - van Heijenoort, Remarks on the computer text of Gödel's dissertation, Aug. 1982 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - 1929: TEXscript (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Gödel dissertation, translation, miscellaneous notes (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - 1930: original German (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - 1940g: original (Box 7, Folder 49)
    - 1930: TEXscript (Box 7, Folder 50)
    - 1930e: FFTG (Box 7, Folder 51)
    - Work on completeness (1930a) (Box 7, Folder 52)
    - 1931 Notes - Kleene (Box 7, Folder 53)
    - 1931 Notes (Box 7, Folder 54)
    - 1931g Original (Box 7, Folder 55)
    - 1931 reprint annotated by KG (Box 7, Folder 56)
    - 1931 (Box 7, Folder 57)
    - 1932a draft translation by Dawson (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Files of van Heijenoort, continued:
    - G 1933e (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - G 1934 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - G 1938 IN (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - G 1938 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - G 1939 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - G 1939a (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - G 1940 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - G 1944 – 5/5/85 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - G 1944 IN (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - G 1944 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - G 1944 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - G 1944 annotations (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - G 1946 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - G 1946 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - G 1947 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - G 1947 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - G 1949 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - G 1949a (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - G 1952 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - G 1958 Dilectica original [photocopy] (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - G 1958 IN (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - G 1958 notes (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - G 1958 Goldfarb translation (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - G 1958 old (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - G 1958 Draft (rought) by JvH July 27, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - G 1958 Draft by JvH July 27, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - G 1958 Translation by SBM-JvH, draft of Sept. 18, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - G 1958 – I (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - G 1958 – II (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - G 1958 English translation by SBM-JvH, draft (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - G 1958 Dawson's remarks on SBM-JvH translation (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - G 1958 SF's remarks on SBM-JvH translation (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - G 1958 Draft of English translation by SBM and JvH June 1984 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - G 1958 Translation revised by SBM and JvH June 1984 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - G 1958 latest work (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - G 1958e Printout of 8/27/84 – SBM's remarks (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - G 1958e Printout of 8/27/84 – SF's remarks (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - G 1958e Proofread by JvH on Jan.9, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - G 1958 English translation – remarks (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - G 1958 G Proofread by JvH on Jan. 9, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - G 1964 (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - G 1964 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - G 1965 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - G 1972 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - G 1972a (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - G 1972a IN draft by Kreisel (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - G 1972a IN – Webb (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - G 1974 IN – Fenstad (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - G copyrights (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - G contract (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - G Bauer – Mengelbert (things to be taken up with) (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - G Correspondence with Herbrand IN (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Very current (in progress at time of death) (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - G editing (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - G Volume I misprints (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - G Contents II (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - G Bernays correspondence (Zurich): listings (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - G non-current (misc. memoranda, mostly re Volume I) (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - G Volume 3 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - G * 1930c Konigsberg lecture on incompleteness (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - G * 1930c Konigsberg lecture on incompleteness (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - G Herbrand Bericht (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - G * 1938c Williamsberg (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Files of van Heijenoort, continued, and files of S. Feferman:
    - G *1939b N.D. GCH I-IV (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - G *1939b continued (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - G Notes on Herbrand (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - G 1950 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Arbetishefte / Results on Foundations: indices and heading lists (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - G Arbetishefte notes (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - G Arbetishefte notes (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - G Arbetishefte Max-Phil (Takenti) (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - G Material sent by Dawson, August 13, 1982 (German translation of Einstein paper, Steinitz's theorem, rotating universes) (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - G Material sent by Dawson, August 17, 1982 (B&P 3rd ed., Boron's Dialectica translation, Gibbs, 1933 AMS lecture, Kant-Einstein, NYPS-1934) (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - G Kant / relativity theory drafts (some observations) (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - G Some observations…Version A (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - G Some observations…Version B (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - G Some observations…Version C (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - G Is mathematics syntax of language? (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - G Is mathematics syntax of language? (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - G Is mathematics syntax of language? (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - G Some considerations… (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Modern developments in foundations…(transcript from Gabelsberger) (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Cohen – Gödel correspondence (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - G's revised translation of 1958 (1972) (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Gödel Project action '94 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Gödel Works IV – general planning and issues (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Gödel Project – Cambridge editorial meeting March 1993 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Gödel – Bem. Phil. Math. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Gödel – excerpts from the Max-Phil notebooks (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Gödel Project – active 1992 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Gödel IV-V jacket material (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Gödel Project – recent 1989-90 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Gödel Project – grant ext. plans 1992-94 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Gödel Project – appearance of Vol. III (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Minutes of Gödel Editorial Board Jan. 1991 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Gödel Editorial Board meeting / work assignments Jan. 1989 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - R. Thomas / R. Tieszn *1961 flap (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Gödel Project action 1990-91 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    - Gödel Nachlass overview/inventory for Vol. III (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Arbeitshefte: index and headings (Box 9, Folder 37)
    - Nagayama – Gödel Project work (Box 9, Folder 38)
    - E. Kohler – correspondence 1990-91 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Nagayama – Gabelsberger transcription (Box 9, Folder 40)
    - What Have We Learned from the Gödel Project? [Feferman's] talk in Stockholm Sept. 1, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Gödel Project – editorial correspondence, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Baaz – letter to Dawson, Dec. 19, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - G Bauer-Mengelberg to S. Feferman (Copyright memo) 1983 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - G Bauer-Mengelberg to Feferman 1984 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - G Brown to JWD (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - Bauer-Mengelberg letter to Gödel, Feb. 21, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - Bauer-Mengelberg to JvH, 1982-86 (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Church letter to Kleene, Nov. 29, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - G Dawson to SBM (Stefan Bauer-Mengelberg) (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - G Dawson to JvH, 1982-86 (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - G Dawson to Editors, 1982-86 (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Taussky-Todd, "Remembrance of Kurt Gödel," Engineering & Science, Winter 1988 (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Anellis, Irving H. "Jean van Heijenoort, his life and his contributions to logic" – typescript, ca. 1985 (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - Files of van Heijenoort, continued, and files of S. Feferman:
    - Dawson to SF 1982-85 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Dawson to SK 1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Dreben-Gödel correspondence 1966-70 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Dreben-Gödel correspondence; copies of batch given by B. D, to JvH on Oct. 15, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Feferman to Dreben 1985 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Feferman to Kleene (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Feferman to Kreisel (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Feferman to Troelstra (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Feferman to editors (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Feferman to JvH (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Feferman to various (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Feferman correspondence on behalf of Gödel Project 1982-85 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Gödel letter to Balas [transcript] 1970 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Bernays 1942 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Bernays 1976 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Bernays, "Sur le platonisme…" (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Bernays, "Quelques points essentials…" (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Bernays, "Mathematische existenz…" (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Gödel letter to Brutian, Dec. 10, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Gödel/Buchi correspondence (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Gödel letter to Burks [published version] (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Gödel correspondence with Davis (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Finsler/Gödel correspondence (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Gödel responses to Grandjean (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Gödel correspondence with Kleene (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Gödel correspondence with Quine (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Gödel letter to Reid, March 22, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Gödel letter to Schilpp, Feb. 3, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Henson to van Heijenoort (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Kleene to editors (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Kleene to SF (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - Kleene to JvH (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Kleene to JvH Oct. 30, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Kurepa to JvH (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Marcus to SF (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Moore to editors (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Moore to JvH 1982-84 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - Moore to JvH 1985-86 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - Moore to various (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Quine to van Heijenoort (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - SK to SF, GM, JvH March 28, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - JvH / Kleene – controversy on underlining (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - van Heijenoort to JWD (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - van Heijenoort to SBM (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - van Heijenoort to editors (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - van Heijenoort to BD (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - van Heijenoort to Goldfarb (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - van Heijenoort to SK (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - van Heijenoort correspondence with Lauener (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - van Heijenoort to GM 1982-84 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - van Heijenoort to Moore 1985 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - van Heijenoort to Webb (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - van Heijenoort to SF (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - van Heijenoort correspondence on behalf of Gödel Project (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Wang to SF (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Webb letter to van Heijenoort Nov. 13, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Weyhrauch, Yasuko to editors (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Gödel – Hao Wang correspondence (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Gödel – Bernays correspondence 1939-59 (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Gödel – Bernays correspondence 1960-63 (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Gödel – Bernays correspondence 1965-75 (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Gödel, "Some considerations leading…" (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Gabelsberger (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Trial translations from Gabelsberger (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Gabelsberger from Max X (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Materials sent as appendices to NSF proposal (1) (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Materials sent as appendices to NSF proposal (2) (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Index miscellany (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Gödel lecture on completeness May 14, 1930 (?) (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Transcriptions from Gabelsberger (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Transcriptions from Gabelsberger – Phil-Max (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Transcriptions from Gabelsberger – "Results on Founcations" (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Dawson, "The Papers of Kurt Gödel an Inventory" July 1984 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Assorted photocopies (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Translations of AC index (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Papers from the Nachlass (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Photocopy of notebook [original manuscript, in English] (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Logic lectures, 0, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Logic lectures, I, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Logic lectures, II, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Logic lectures, III, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Logic lectures, IV, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Logic lectures, V, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Logic lectures, VI, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Logic lectures, VII, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Continuum lectures, I, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Continuum lectures, II, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Continuum lectures, III, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Continuum lectures, IV, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Continuum lectures, V, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Sources, photocopies, misc. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Book cover layouts (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Records, Accession ARCH-2008-054
  - Front matter, Vol. IV (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photo information (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Angoff (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Balas (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Behmann – correspondence with editors, 1994-2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Behmann – introductory note (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Behmann – typescripts and TeXscripts (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Behmann – photocopies of original letters (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Behmann – translation (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Behmann – transcriptions, text and correspondence re (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Behmann – references (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bernays – correspondence information (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Bernays – introductory note (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bernays – current text (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bernays – TeXscripts (1 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Bernays – TeXscripts (2 of 2) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Bernays – TeXscripts (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Bernays – TeXscript 10/00 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bernays – TeXscript 12/98 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Bernays – TeXscript 4/94 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Bernays – TeXscript 9/93 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Bernays – edited typescripts (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Bernays – photocopies of original correspondence, 1930-42 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bernays – photocopies of original correspondence, 1956-61 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Bernays – photocopies of original correspondence, 1962-65 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Bernays – photocopies of original correspondence, 1966-70 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Bernays – photocopies of original correspondence, 1971-75 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Bernays – translations, TeXscripts (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Bernays – translations, typescripts (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Bernays correspondence, textual notes (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bernays – references (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Blackwell (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Bohnert (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Boone (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Boone – references (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Brutian (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Büchi (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Carnap (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Carnap - TeXscripts (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Church – typescripts, TeXscripts (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Cohen (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Dreben (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Feigl – typescripts, TeXscripts (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Feigl – photocopies of original correspondence (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Finsler (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Follett (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Goddard (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Gödel to Marianne Gödel – introductory note (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Gödel to Marianne Gödel – TeXscripts (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Gödel to Marianne Gödel – translations (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Grandjean (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Greenberg (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Günther – correspondence of editors (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Günther – introductory note (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Günther – TeXscripts (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Günther – TeXscripts (2 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Günther – typescripts (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Günther – translation (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Günther – photocopies of original correspondence (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence of Henkin with Russell and Church re Gödel's work (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Henkin (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Herbrand – introductory note (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Herbrand – TeXscripts (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Herbrand – translations (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Heyting – introductory note and correspondence of editors (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Heyting – TeX (1 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Heyting – TeX (2 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Heyting – TeX (3 of 3) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Heyting – typescripts (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Heyting – photocopies of original correspondence (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Heyting – translations (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Heyting – references (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Honderich (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Hwastecki (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Menger – TeXscripts (1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Menger – TeXscripts (2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Menger – photocopies of original correspondence from IAS (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Menger – photocopies of original correspondence from IIT (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Menger – translations (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Nagel – introductory note and correspondence of editors (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Nagel (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Perlis (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Pitts (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Plumer (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Popper (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Post (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Rappaport (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Rautenberg (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Reid (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Robinson – introductory note (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Robinson – TeXscripts and photocopies of original correspondence (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Robinson – photocopies of original correspondence from Yale (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Russell (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Sawyer (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Schilpp – introductory note (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Schilpp – TeXscripts (1 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Schilpp – TeXscripts (2 of 2) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Schilpp – photocopies of original correspondence (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Schilpp – photocopies of original correspondence from SIU (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Seelig (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Skolem (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Suppes (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Tarski – TeX (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Tarski – photocopies of original correspondence (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Thirring (Box 9, Folder 3)